

Stylianos Vogiatzis

stelios_vogiatzis@hotmail.com

(+34) 664 646 904

Thesaloniki, Greece

CERTIFICATIONS

Teaching Proficiency Certificate

MCP: Microsoft 365, SaaS Cloud



MCP: Microsoft Azure, IaaS

PaaS & SaaS Cloud



SKILLS

Leadership



Active Listener Communication



Team Player



HONORS & AWARDS

- Local Committee in Aiesec won the national award in CRM.
- Running the 38th Official Authentic Marathon in Athens at November 2021.
- · Being in the Coordinating Comitee of my High School as a representative.
- Excellent Distinction in High School.

LANGUAGES







Greek

English

Spanish

INTERESTS



Travelling



Reading





SUMMARY

Graduated from Applied Infromatics and specialized in Management of Technologies. Highly motivated and Accountable, Team Player, Structured, Self Confident with strong Tech skills and ability to research issues and provide Solutions. Currently in pursuit of working experiences and self development. Certified with Teaching Proficiency and as Microsoft Professional in all the cloud models.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

1GlobalTranslator INTERN

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023, ES

- Document Management & Integration of them in cloud.
- Collect, Analyze & Manage data of payments and bank transactions for clients and suppliers.
- · Manage the IT services of the company.

TEAM LEADER Kalivas Summer Camp

Jun - Sep 2017, GR

- Team Leader in houses of 15+ people, ages 14~16.
- · Activity leader in sports events of the camp.
- Assisting the event managers.

INTERNATIONAL EXPERIENCE

PARTICIPANT Erasmus+ Projects

- · Participated in three Erasmus+ Projects in Italy, Latvia and Bulgaria.
- · Developed Skills to be competitive in the Labor Market & Learning and Experimenting Interculturality in Latvia.
- · Developed Skills of Youth Entrepreunership Based on Good Practices in Bulgaria.
- Developed a better understanding in the range of European cultures, languages and values in Italy.
- · Daily reflection and implementation of the acquired skills in the European Markets.

Aiesec

- · Create new customers with targeted offers.
- · Standing Booths & University Relations.

GLOBAL VOLUNTEER PARTNER

· Attending to projects of developing Soft Skills.

Erasmus Studies Network PARTNER

Sep 2019 - Sep 2022, GR

Sep 2018 - Jul 2019, GR

- Attend to Projects of enhancing soft skills.
- Organize events for the incoming erasmus students.
- · Guide newcomer foreigners to my city.

EDUCATION HISTORY

University of Macedonia

Sep 2018 - Sep 2022, GR

University of Malaga

Feb 2021 - Sep 2021, ES